

DANIEL SAMUEL SALVADOR

Customer Service Representative

- +9351 6317965
- Danielsamuelsalvador@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/daniel-samuelsalvador-789ba0161/
- 173 Tomas Arguelles St., Brgy Santol Quezon City,

EDUCATION

Highschool

Don Bosco Technical College
2011 - 2015

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Don Bosco Technical College

2021 - 2023

EXPERTISE

Web Design

Web Development

Graphic Design

Sales

CERTIFICATES

Cybersecurity Administration

PIPEDA

ABOUT ME

Hardworking Customer Service Representative with nearly 2 years of experience working in Sales, Reservations and Healthcare. Trained in project and time management with extensive knowledge and proven multitasking abilities. Committed to maintaining professional relationships with clients to increase profitability and drive business results.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Sept 2020 - Jul 2021 WNS | Pasig

Associate Ops

- Consulted with outside parties to resolve discrepancies and create expert solutions.
- Used data entry skills to accurately document and input statements.
- Trained to handle Medical bills and Responded to customer concerns and questions on daily basis.
- Mar 2019 Sep 2019 Concentrix | Mandaluyong

Customer Service Representative

- Maintained customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns.
- Updated account information to maintain customer records.
- Trained to handle customer calls, emails and chats (2 customer chats at a time)

6 Feb 2019 - Mar 2019 Alorica | Makati

Customer Sales Representative

- Assisted customers with setting appointments, shipping and special order requests, and arranging merchandise pick-up at other locations.
- Answered constant flow of customer calls with minimal wait times.
- Clarified customer issues and determined root cause of problems to resolve product or service complaints.